{
    "subject": "resource/Khaled_Melliti",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tunis",
    "human_readable": "Khaled Melliti was born in Tunis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9064300060272217,
            "question": "Where was Khaled Melliti born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967494964599609,
            "question": "Name the city where Khaled Melliti was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8371536135673523,
            "question": "In what year was Khaled Melliti born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7030007243156433,
            "question": "What nationality is Khaled Melliti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48558178544044495,
            "question": "What is Khaled Melliti known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46544745564460754,
            "question": "Where did Khaled Melliti live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29924675822257996,
            "question": "Is Khaled Melliti a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29103919863700867,
            "question": "Tell me about Khaled Melliti's early life."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24685968458652496,
            "question": "Does Khaled Melliti have any notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2294018268585205,
            "question": "What kind of work does Khaled Melliti do?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Khaled Melliti was born in Tunis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Khaled Melliti have any notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tell me about Khaled Melliti's early life.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Khaled Melliti a public figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5037_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the document with the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5037/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt`, which states: `Place of Birth: Tunis`. This confirms that Khaled Melliti was born in Tunis."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}